Maybe I haven't gotten as out
of shape as I worried I was.
I can still make it as a swordsman, I think.
Time to try some support magic, too.
Strength Up.
Support magic improves its
targets' physical abilities,
or strengthens their equipment.
The caster can not only use it to help his
party members, he can put it on himself.
With spells to increase both attack and
defense, it's something every party needs.
EPISODE 1: THE JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES
BECOMES A SWORDSMAN ONCE MORE
But it has a weakness, too.
Time.
Three minutes exactly, huh?
Strength Up.
Support magic doesn't last forever.
And an individual's magic resistance
changes the amount of time it lasts.
In my case, it lasts 180 seconds.
Three seconds left...
Strength Up!
I have to keep a close eye on the state of
the battle, and cast it at just the right time.
Enchanters who use support magic are
constantly in a race against time.
Normally, you don't try to use
it while swinging a sword around.
But in my case...
We're going to have to ask you
to leave the hero's party today.
Is this some kind of joke, Oliver?
It's not, Orhun.
What are you talking about?
We're childhood friends!
Comrades who've always been together!
Yes. Until now, I've given you plenty of
chances because you're from the same village.
But from now on,
you won't be able to keep up.
Why not just come out and say it?
Tell him he's just slowing us down.
Anneli? Derick?
You just aren't strong enough.
So we're going to ask you
to leave the hero's party.
Oliver...
The party that Oliver and I formed eight years
ago achieved S-Rank in just a few years.
We were the first to reach the 94th
floor in the Southern Great Dungeon.
People began to call us the "Hero's Party."
Perhaps you're right.
Maybe I'm not strong enough.
But that goes for all of us. At this rate...
Orhun, we didn't understand
how important it was
to have an enchanter who
could use support magic.
But...
In the joint raid last month,
we were able to see how incredible the
other S-Rank party's enchanters were.
And we understood how weak
your support magic is.
Of course it is.
I'm supposed to be a swordsman.
That's why I created my own original magic.
Shut up!
You converted because Oliver was
better with a blade than you!
And now, you're not a very
good enchanter either.
Are you in a position to complain?
We needed an enchanter,
so I converted because I was the one
who had the most aptitude for it.
I've invented my own kind of
magic to make up for my flaws.
And we've survived even on the deepest
floors of the dungeon because of that...
We've already found a
replacement enchanter.
I'm sorry, but that's how it's going to be.
We're the Hero's Party!
We have to keep going!
And we can't do that with you,
is what we're saying.
What?
Is that how you treat me after
all we've been through together?
There's no place for me
here anymore, is there?
Very well. Thanks for everything.
Magic, sword fighting... you can do a lot,
but only at an A-Rank level.
But you kept telling us what to do,
and it was pissing us off.
Do you know what they call people like you?
A jack-of-all-trades!
A jack-of-all-trades, huh?
All right. A swordsman and an enchanter...
This new style I've developed
that combines both...
I'm adaptable enough to pull it off.
So that nobody will call me a
jack-of-all-trades anymore...
Someday, I'll be an adventurer
who can do anything.
And now I'm registered with
the teleportation crystal.
I can start from Floor 7 next time.
That's enough for today...
Hurry! Come on!
What?
Damn it! How did this happen?
There's nothing we can do about it.
There're so many orcs...
But we left that girl behind!
What?
We would've been wiped out!
I made the right call!
B-But that doesn't mean...
She just joined us today...
of course I'm going to prioritize
you, my old friends!
I shouldn't get involved.
She just had bad luck joining
up with them, is all.
But...
I know how much it hurts for
your party to abandon you.
I made the right call!
If you don't like it,
are you going to go save her?
No way! I can't...
I can't bear to listen to this.
Who are you?
You left that girl to die.
Now you're just making excuses
instead of going to save her.
Guys like you piss me off more than anything.
You... How dare you?!
Even if I stayed back there,
I couldn't save her alone!
Then just lie there.
Where is she?
Tell me where you left her to die!
Stay away...
Stay away from me!
I can't handle so many...
Sister...!
Somebody...
save me!
Aeroshock!
Who is he? A swordsman?
Strength Up!
Technical Up!
Support magic?
Is he a swordsman? Or an enchanter?
Sharpness Up!
Wow... I've never seen
anyone fight like this!
There's a lot of them.
I can see why a low-ranking party would run.
But me...
I can handle this alone!
He's...
so strong!
You okay?
I'm alive...
Okay, I'll be going.
Wait!
Let me thank you properly.
Thank you so much!
My name is Sophia Claudel!
Claudel?
That crest...
Um...
Oh, no, I'm sorry for not giving my name.
I'm Orhun Dura.
Orhun...
A wonderful name.
So, Orhun... would it be all right if
I treated you to dinner as thanks?
I didn't save you because I wanted thanks...
Please!
O-Okay...
Thank you.
Orhun, we're here!
This place isn't expensive,
but it's really good!
Just like I thought,
it's one of the Rabbits' shops...
I could guess from the crest on her cape,
but she's clearly from the
Night Sky Silver Rabbits,
one of the biggest guilds
in the kingdom of Nohitant.
The Night Sky Silver Rabbits are one of
the most popular clans in the kingdom...
After all, she's part of them.
Sister?
What are you doing here?
Oh, Sophia?
I had a meeting near here today.
So... who are you with?
It's too soon for you to have a boyfriend!
Orhun Dura?
It's been a while, Selma Claudel....
Orhun, you know her?
Yes, of course.
Selma Claudel is the leader of the S-Rank party
that's the most powerful in the Silver Rabbits...
and the continent's most powerful enchanter.
She's the one who made enchanters famous,
and created the idea of different
party members having different roles.
Attackers to take down the enemy.
Defenders to tank the hits.
Supporters helping in the rear.
Splitting the party into these
three roles was her idea.
It changed the way adventurers think
about going into the dungeons forever.
The Hero's Party is no exception.
That's why I had to go from being
a swordsman to an enchanter.
And it was seeing her in the
raid last month that caused
Oliver and the others to get rid of me.
I thought they were just in the same clan...
I didn't expect them to be siblings.
But... Why is she mad at me?
So you're going after my
fourteen-year-old sister?
That's very brave of you.
Oh, so that's it.
You've got it all wrong.
Yes, I was about to eat dinner with her.
But my intentions are
completely pure, I assure you.
What, so my Sophia's not good enough for you?
Wow, this is annoying.
Sister! Stop!
Don't be rude to the man who saved my life!
Saved your life?
Don't tell me...
Did you go to the dungeon alone?
Um...
Did you?
Yeah...
I told you we'd be going into the
Great Dungeon the day after tomorrow,
and to stay put for a few days...
I'm sorry.
I see. So she was dungeon-delving
without telling her clan.
Well, it seems you're safe, so I
won't give you a hard time about it.
But from now on, no going off on your own.
Okay...
Orhun, I guess you saved
my sister. Thank you.
I'm sorry for being so rude.
It's fine.
I haven't seen you since the raid.
That's right.
It's our first time talking like this.
Yes.
You two knew each other?
We met during the raid last month.
I see.
We're both enchanters,
so we were stationed together.
You took command and I helped you.
And you helped a lot.
It was just what I expected.
It's like you've known him for a while.
What, Sophia? You don't know about Orhun?
No. Is he famous?
Of course he is!
He's a member of the Hero's Party!
Um, uh... well...
Don't get so flustered.
And I'm not a hero anymore.
You're not? Did you leave your party?
Yes. Yesterday.
Why would they let somebody like you go?
Well, they had their reasons.
Both of us agreed to it.
I see...
So you're free at the moment, right?
Well, I suppose.
Is she going to recruit
me to the Silver Rabbits?
If you're not busy...
Sorry!
Um, I don't want to be in a
clan or party for a while...
I think you've got the wrong idea.
I've got the perfect job for you.
Job?
I want you to go with our clan on
our teaching expedition tomorrow.
I'll make sure you're paid.
Teaching expedition?
Just what the name implies.
It's to teach the new recruits.
You can think of it as on-the-job training.
You want me to go along?
A group of A-Ranks and higher
will lead the new recruits.
We'll spend three days going 50 floors
down in the Southern Great Dungeon.
Three days?
Even the best new adventurers
would take six months to a year.
That's a pretty crazy schedule.
It's crazy, but not impossible
if you take the shortest route.
But...
And our sponsors are insisting...
I guess the Silver Rabbits
have it rough, huh?
But what you're proposing
is crazy enough that
you should've been able to
turn down your sponsors.
If you're doing it anyway...
Is there some other reason?
If new recruits who wouldn't
be able to beat a floor boss
on their own can go exploring
in the deeper floors,
it'll strengthen the clan as a whole.
He realized just from the few things I said?
He's smarter than I thought.
In the dungeons, you need to
defeat the floor bosses that
appear every ten floors to go any deeper.
It's common for new recruits to be
injured or killed during these battles.
But if a veteran adventurer
can take the the boss down,
then all they have to do is register with
the crystal on the next floor to go deeper.
So we want you to go with us.
This seems like a really important
mission for the Silver Rabbits.
Is it okay for an outsider
like me to be there?
Orhun.
I respect you.
Selma respects me as an enchanter?
To be honest, that makes me
happy, but why would she?
I was banished from the
Hero's Party for being too weak.
Because my magic was worse
than hers during the raid.
And I have to go back to being an enchanter?
After what just happened to me?
Of course I'll regret it.
I'm happy you think so highly of me,
but I have other plans.
Orhun...
U-Um, Orhun... I'm going too.
So it would make me really
happy if you went with me!
Please... please!
Are you busy...?
Let me think about it.
Orhun.
Okay, got it.
Just to be clear, I've converted
to being a swordsman.
A swordsman?
Yes.
It seems you respect me as an enchanter.
But if I'm going, it will be as a swordsman.
Why did you do that?
Of course she's surprised.
But this is something I won't give up.
Okay, that's fine.
It doesn't matter.
If things get bad, he'll go back
to his main job of enchanter.
If you're coming, please be at the
Silver Rabbit HQ tomorrow morning.
All right.
Good evening.
Oh, Orhun?
Are you still open?
I was about to close up.
But take your time.
Today was another busy day.
Glad you're doing well.
Thanks to you advertising the store
after you became a top adventurer.
I really am grateful.
Old man, sorry.
Orhun?
I'm not a member of the Hero's Party anymore.
I won't be able to advertise
for you any longer.
Now that I'm not a hero,
nobody will listen to a thing I say.
I'm grateful to you.
I always have been, and I always will be.
You're still you,
whether you're a hero or not.
So let me say it again... thank you.
You'd thank me... someone like me?
Is that strange?
I know what you've done, how hard
you've worked, better than anyone.
So I know that from here on out,
you'll be hearing even more "thank yous."
These words mean that there are
people out there who need you.
Treasure those words
every time you hear them.
Old man...
Things are just getting started, Orhun.
Just do as you think best.
Live for yourself. Help others.
Whatever happens, I'm on your side.
Thank you, old man...
JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES, PARTY OF NONE
Good morning, Selma.
You came, huh?
Follow me.
You look livelier than you did yesterday.
I guess you feel relieved to
be out of the Hero's Party.
Yes, something like that.